# KEVIN CALLAGHAN





#### EDUCATION

FULL STACK CODING BOOTCAMP The University of Texas 2023

MARKETING, B.B.A. Stephen F. Austin State Univ. 2004 - 2010

### SKILLS

HTML5/CSS3

React

Node.js

Express.js

MERN

Javascript

MySQL and MongoDB

Communication

Problem Solving

Client Service

Technical Support

Top Rated eBay Seller

Teamwork

#### PROFILE

As a recent full stack web development bootcamp grad, I bring a unique advantage of having spent 9 years immersed in the client side of the industry providing client services, technical support, customizing html/css design, and training clients to effectively utilize custom web applications, giving me the unique ability to effectively communicate and collaborate with clients during the development process. While I may be new to the coding aspect, my deep familiarity with the industry allows me to quickly adapt and contribute my expertise to development projects. Additional experience in online sales via community eccommerce websites.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

PRIVATE EBAY SELLER Houston, TX | 2021 - 2023

> Achieved the Top Rated eBay Seller ranking for excellent customer service over hundreds of transactions.

TECHNICAL SUPPORT REPRESENTATIVE Netsential, Houston, TX | 2011 - 2020

Netsential is a small web development firm which focuses on developing custom tools and modules used across various industries in government, law enforcement, and the private sector.

- Presented new programming projects to the development team and collaborated with clients to customize the applications based on their specific needs.
- Communicated with clients to resolve any problems or meet client requests after product launch, including website and application maintenance and upgrades.
- Trained new and existing clients to use our custom web programs.

ACCOUNT MANAGER / SALES REPRESENTATIVE TruGreen, Houston, TX | Jan 2010 - Dec 2010

TruGreen provides year-round residential lawn care & tree/shrub services.

• Sold residential lawn care services in-person via door-to-door sales and through telemarketing to personal contacts and cold-calls while meeting weekly sales goals

#### **INTERN**

Bradmark Technologies, Houston, TX | 2002

Bradmark is a Houston-based software company which provides industry leading database management solutions and services.

• Performed various tasks including data entry, inventory, and shipping.